SPRING SCRIPT is a casual handwritten font. 

It has a little messy look and some words may not work well but some looks perfect for logotype. Same applies especially to all caps. Give it a try ;)

Free for personal use only. For commercial use please donate or contact@rolandhuse.com 

Also if you have character / language extension requests, any questions or feedback.

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.
You MAY NOT redistribute this font.

Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Runes-And-Fonts/123221817784772

